Catherine (Catie) O'Connor

2150 North Lincoln Park West \circ Chicago, IL 60614 \circ 480-459-6014 \circ catieoconnor19@yahoo.com

CAREER PROFILE

Escrow Closing coordinator with 1.5+ years experience in the real estate title industry. Team player in professional corporate setting and former Division 1 student athlete in two sports, with 4+ years' customer service experience.

My core competencies include: written communication, verbal communication, team collaboration, attention to detail. My skills include: Microsoft office proficiency, Ramquest proficiency, time management, prioritization, and knowledge of computer applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Stewart Title Guaranty

Commercial Escrow Assistant October 2021 to present

Greater Illinois Title Company

Escrow Coordinator March 2020 to October 2021

- Prepare CD's and closing statements.
- Communicate with attorneys and lenders to review closing costs and obtain required documents.
- Address customer concerns and requests via phone and email.
- Schedule closing appointments and send confirmations.
- Collaborate with a team of Closers to ensure a smooth closing experience for all parties.

Holladay Properties

Seasonal Property Maintenance June 2018 to August 2018

- Assigned to property maintenance in a suburban business park environment
- Demonstrated the ability to work effectively alone and with others
- Collaborate with team members to ensure building owner and tenant satisfaction

Jimmy John's Gourmet Sandwiches

In-shop worker *June 2014 to June 2017*

- Multi task: make and wrap sandwiches, dish washing, general cleaning, cash register duties, answer delivery phone calls, customer service.
- Detail oriented: accurately and efficiently prepare customized sandwiches.
- Urgency: ability to complete orders and other tasks in a fast paced environment.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Management *April 2019*

Davenport University – Grand Rapids, MI

Associate in Medical Assisting *April 2017*

Davenport University – Grand Rapids, MI

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

USA Rugby DI College 4-time National Champion – Davenport University Women's Rugby Davenport University Women's Hockey ACHA Division 1 team member